ultimatetube.com 2012-03-15

# - Watch Christian Videos - UltimateTube :

* UltimateTube Online Privacy Statement 
* UltimateTube Online is committed to protecting your privacy. This privacy statement explains data collection and use practices of the Christian Videos Site (www.ultimatetube.com) site (the 'Site'); it also does apply to other online or offline Christian Videos sites, products or services. By accessing the Site, you are consenting to the information collection and use practices described in this privacy statement. 
* Collection of your Personal Information 
* We will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you (personal information) or allows us to contact you to provide a service or carry out a transaction that you have requested such as receiving information about UltimateTube products and services, entering a contest, ordering e-mail newsletters, joining a limited-access premium site or service, signing up for an event or training, or when purchasing, downloading and/or registering UltimateTube products. The personal information we collect may include your name, title, company or organization name, work e-mail, work phone, work or home address, information about your job function, information about your company, and credit card information.

The Site may collect certain information about your visit, such as the name of the Internet service provider and the Internet Protocol (IP) address through which you access the Internet; the date and time you access the Site; the pages that you access while at the Site and the Internet address of the Web site from which you linked directly to our site. This information is used to help improve the site, analyze trends and administer the site. Some of our sites collect information about your hardware and software in order to provide a requested service. Windows Update, for example, needs to know information about your computer in order to recommend needed operating system updates.

UltimateTube technical communities provide opportunities to interact with UltimateTube employees, experts, and your peers in order to share knowledge and news about UltimateTube products and related technologies. In order to avoid your e-mail address or other personal information from being gathered and used by others for inappropriate or harmful purposes, Ultimatetube advises that you should be cautious about posting a real e-mail address or other personal information to newsgroups, chats, or other public forums. 

* Use of your Personal Information 
* The personal information collected on this Site will be used to operate the Site and to provide the service(s) or carry out the transaction(s) you have requested or authorized. 

In support of these uses, UltimateTube may use personal information to provide you with more effective customer service, to improve the Site and any related UltimateTube products or services, and to make the Site easier to use by eliminating the need for you to repeatedly enter the same information or by customizing the Site to your particular preference or interests. In order to offer you a more consistent experience in your interactions with UltimateTube, information collected by UltimateTube may be combined with information collected by other UltimateTube services. 

We may use your personal information to provide you with important information about the product or service that you are using, including critical updates and notifications. Additionally, with your permission, we may send you information about other UltimateTube products and services, and/or share information with UltimateTube partners so they may send you information about their products and services. 

We merge site-visitation data with anonymous demographic information for research purposes, and we may use this information in aggregate to provide more relevant content. In some limited-entry sections of UltimateTube, with your approval, we will combine site-visitation data with your personal information in order to provide you with personalized content. If you decline permission, we will not provide you the personalized service and won't merge your personal information with site-visitation data. 

When you sign up for a newsletter or agree to receive promotional e-mail, UltimateTube may use customized links or similar technologies to track e-mail links that you click. We may associate that information with your personal information in order to provide you more focused e-mail communications or purchase information. Each e-mail communication includes an unsubscribe link allowing you to stop delivery of that type of communication. 

Some services on UltimateTube offer individuals the ability to publicly display certain personal information, such as for a UltimateTube partner who wishes to publish contact information as part of offering a business service. Participation in such services is always optional. 

UltimateTube occasionally hires other companies to provide limited services on our behalf, such as Web site hosting, packaging, mailing and delivering prizes, answering customer questions about products and services, and sending information about our products, special offers, and other services. We will only provide those companies the personal information they need to deliver the service. They are required to maintain the confidentiality of the information and are prohibited from using that information for any other purpose. 

UltimateTube may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on UltimateTube or the Site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of UltimateTube and our family of Web sites; or (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of UltimateTube employees or agents, users of UltimateTube products or services, or members of the public. 

Personal information collected on the Site may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which UltimateTube or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities, and by using the Site, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country. UltimateTube abides by the safe harbor framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of data from the European Union. 

* Information Sharing and Disclosure
* UltimateTube.com will never rent, sell, or share your email, physical address or other personal information to a third party, except in the following circumstances:

* We may share your email and/or physical address with our trusted third-party partners for the purpose of providing and operating the UltimateTube.com service. We require that these parties agree to process such information based on our instructions and in compliance with this Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.

* We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims;

* We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of UltimateTube.com's Terms of Service, or as otherwise required by law.

* If UltimateTube.com becomes involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of its assets, we will provide notice before personal information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. 

You may use UltimateTube.com to invite others to view your video channel. UltimateTube will not sell or share the recipients' email addresses, or add them to any mailing lists. 

You do not control who sees your video channel on UltimateTube.com. We provide open access to all of our registered sites. If you do not want your site viewable in our channel guide please edit your preferences on your main profile page.

* Control of your Personal Information 
* Except as otherwise described in this statement, personal information you provide on the Site will not be shared outside of UltimateTube and its controlled subsidiaries and affiliates without your permission. 

Please be aware that this privacy statement and any choices you make on the Site will not necessarily apply to personal information you may have provided to UltimateTube in the context of other, separately operated, UltimateTube products or services. 

UltimateTube may send out periodic e-mails informing you of technical service or security issues related to a product or service you requested, or confirming you requested a product or service. In some services offered by UltimateTube, contact with the customer is an intrinsic part of the service. You will not be able to choose to unsubscribe to these mailings, as they are considered an essential part of the service(s) you have chosen. 

* Access to your Personal Information 
* Some services offered on UltimateTube may collect information that is not accessible. However you can access your personal information by contacting UltimateTube as described at the bottom of this statement, or through alternative means of access described by the service. You can review and edit your personal information by contacting one of our Customer Service representatives Monday through Friday, between the hours of 9 a.m. and 4 p.m. CST at 1-210-588-9533.
* Security of your Personal Information 
* UltimateTube is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. For example, we store the personal information you provide on computer servers with limited access that are located in controlled facilities. Additionally, when we transmit sensitive personal information (such as a credit card number) over the Internet, we protect it through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.
* Protection of Children's Personal Information 
* UltimateTube is a general audience site and does not knowingly collect any personal information from children. 
* Use of Cookies 
* We use cookies on this Site to ensure the integrity of the registration process and to personalize the Site. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a Web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. 

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. For example, if you personalize a web page, or navigate within a site, a cookie helps the site to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of delivering relevant content, eases site navigation, and so on. When you return to the Web site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the site's features that you customized. 

Web beacons, also known as clear gif technology or action tags, may be used to assist in delivering the cookie on our site. This technology is a tool we use to compile aggregated statistics about UltimateTube Web site usage, such as how many visitors clicked on key elements (such as links or graphics) on a UltimateTube Web page, blog or a newsletter. We may share aggregated site statistics with partner companies. 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of this or other Web sites you visit. 

* Use of Web Beacons 
* UltimateTube Web pages may contain electronic images known as Web beacons - sometimes called single-pixel gifs - that allow UltimateTube to count users who have visited those pages and to deliver co-branded services. UltimateTube may include Web beacons in promotional e-mail messages or newsletters in order to determine whether messages have been opened and acted upon. 

Some of these Web beacons may be placed by third party service providers to help determine the effectiveness of our advertising campaigns or email communications. These Web beacons may be used by these service providers to place a persistent cookie on your computer. Doing this allows the service provider to recognize your computer each time you visit certain pages or emails and compile anonymous information in relation to those page views. UltimateTube prohibits Web beacons from being used to collect or access your personal information. 

* Enforcement of this Privacy Statement 
* If you have questions regarding this statement, you should contact [UltimateTube](mailto:privacy@ultimatetube.com) . 
* Changes to this Statement 
* We may occasionally update this privacy statement. When we do, we will also revise the "last updated" date at the top of the privacy statement. For material changes to this privacy statement, we will notify you either by placing a prominent notice on the home page of our Web site or by directly sending you a notification. We encourage you to periodically review this privacy statement to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. Your continued use of the service constitutes your agreement to this privacy statement and any updates.
* Contact Information 
* UltimateTube welcomes your comments regarding this privacy statement. If you believe that UltimateTube has not adhered to this privacy statement, please contact [privacy@ultimatetube.com](mailto:privacy@ultimatetube.com) or via support ticket at the address provided below, and we will use reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem. UltimateTube 
* Date Last Modified: 
* This Privacy Notice was last modified October 15 , 2009.
